

ANTONELLA DI TURRIS

ENGINEERING STUDENT

PROFILE

Engineering student with extensive professional experience in several fields, specialized in carrying out tasks simultaneously, in Spanish, English and Portuguese. Over the years I developed a great capacity for teamwork and effective communication.

I like challenges and I am currently doing IT training, focusing on developing my career in the systems and development area.

SKILLS

Python	
Sql	
Javascript	
Html	
CSS	
Vue	
Looker Studio	

CONTACT

Date of Birth: 03/20/1994 Address: Buenos Aires, Argentina Cell: 549-11-3481-2721 E-Mail: amditurris@hotmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistance Supervisor

ASSIST CARD (04/2022 - 09/2022)

- Virtual supervision in night shift (00:00 to 08:00) to coordinators from Brazil, Peru and Argentina.
- Monitoring and evaluation of the performance of the coordinators, together with periodic feedback in order to improve it.
- Assignment and control of tasks based on the skills and strengths of each coordinator.
- Audit of cases and medical budgets, elevating to management what corresponds.
- Containment and resolution of complaints.

Assistance supervision support

ASSIST CARD (11/2021 - 31-03-2022)

- Supervision support by helping Jr. coordinators in different situations.
- Daily administrative reports.
- Containment of customer complaints.

Assistance Coordinator

ASSIST CARD (09/2019 - 10/2021

- -Comprehensive assistance to clients through multiple platforms.
- -Medical coordination in Spanish, English and Portuguese all over the world.
- -Medical and cost evaluation with the indicated sectors.
- -Daily monitoring of hospitalized patients.

Customer Service Representative

Berlitz Argentine (10/2017 - 03/2018)

- Reception, organization and collection at the language study center.

Media Assistance

Mediacom (08/2015 - 08/2016)

- Daily monitoring of the performance of advertising campaigns on various platforms.

Reception and manager

Nobel Salud (02/2013 - 04/2014)

- Administrative and in charge of external clinics.

EDUCATION

100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp

Udemy - (08/22 -present)

Biq Data

Codo a Codo 4.0 - (08/22 - 12/22)

Full stack - Python

Codo a Codo 4.0 - (02/22 -07/22)

Chemical and Food Engineering

UBA (2015 - present)

Automotive Mechanical and Electrical Technician

ITCA (2014-2016)

LANGUAGES

English Advanced Portuguese Advanced Spanish Native